galacasino.com 2013-08-06

# Gala Casino Privacy Policy Gala Casino Privacy Policy

  1. Objectives of this privacy policy
  2. Information collected
  3. Means of collecting and processing data 
  4. Information use
  5. Access to personal information
  6. Cookies
  7. Consent to security review 
  8. Security of personal information
  9. International transfers
  10. Consent to privacy policy

**1\. OBJECTIVES OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY** (back to top)

1.1 In this Privacy Policy, as in the general terms and conditions ("the terms"), references to the "company", "we" or "us" will apply to the GalaCasino.com website and/or Gala Interactive (Gibraltar) Limited, which is a subsidiary of Gala Coral Group Limited.  
Gala Interactive (Gibraltar) Limited is licensed by the Government of Gibraltar and regulated by the [Gibraltar Gambling Commissioner](http://www.gibraltar.gov.gi/remotegambling) under Gibraltar's Gambling Act 2005.  
Further, any reference to ‘You' or ‘Your' refers to any person who opens an account with us and in effect signs up to and accepts these T's and C's.  
1.2 We are required by law, specifically the Data Protection Act 1998, to comply with the data protection requirements regarding the use of any personal information collected from You, while using the website. We respect Your privacy and to support this committment to protecting Your personal information, this Privacy Policy has been created to confirm:

  * what information is gathered when You use the website (collectively referred to as the "Service");
  * why we gather this information; and
  * how we use the collected information.

1.3 We may occasionally make changes to this Privacy Policy and these will be highlighted to You when we publish the updated terms on the website. In order to monitor any changes we advise You to review the Privacy Policy regularly.

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTED** (back to top)

2.1 Personal information which may be used to identify an individual could include the following:

  * first and last name;
  * date of birth;
  * credit or debit card information;
  * home or other physical address;
  * e-mail address; and/or
  * phone number or other contact information.

2.2 Personal information may be requested during account registration or at other times, when using the service. The personal information collected may include:

  * contact information, for example a telephone number;
  * shipping information;
  * billing information;
  * transaction history;
  * website preferences; and/or
  * feedback regarding the service.

2.3 This information is held by us on servers located in Gibraltar **.** However, this information may occasionally be held in other locations. Our servers also keep a log of Your activities which is essential for the quality and provision of the service, although this information is not collected without Your knowledge. This activity log includes administrative and traffic information such as:

  * source IP address;
  * time and date of access;
  * web page/s visited;
  * language used;
  * software crash reports; and
  * type of browser used.

2.4 If there is a legal requirement, or we believe such action is necessary, we may reveal Your personal information for the following reasons **:**

  * to comply with any legal process served on us, the website or the service;
  * to protect and defend our rights of property or the interests of sporting or other qualified bodies; or
  * to protect the personal safety of users of the service or the public.

2.5  We may decide to share Your information and identity with other online gaming sites, banks, credit card companies and appropriate agencies, if You are found to have undertaken the following:

  * cheated or attempted to defraud us or our affiliates or any other user of the service in any way, including but not limited to:
  * game manipulation or payment fraud;
  * suspicion of fraudulent payment, including use of stolen credit cards;
  * any other fraudulent activity, including any chargebacks or other reversal of payment; or
  * prohibited transactions, including money laundering.

2.6  We may share Your personal information with regulators, sports' governing bodies and other authorised bodies, including the police, for the purposes of investigating any actual or suspected criminal activity or other regulatory matters.

**3\. MEANS OF COLLECTING AND PROCESSING DATA** (back to top)

3.1 **** As detailed in section 2, we may automatically collect certain data and receive personal information via Your use of our products and services, or other communications within the company. Personal information may be recorded on the telephone, or used for training purposes or by Customer Services.  
3.2 Personal information may also come from online vendors and service providers who refer You to the service and from customer lists lawfully acquired from third-party vendors. Third-party service providers may be appointed to provide technical support, process Your online transactions and maintain Your online accounts. We may have access to any information provided to such vendors, service providers and third party e-commerce services and we will use the personal information as detailed in section 4 below.  
3.3 This information may only be revealed to our staff and third parties involved in the transaction process and the support of Your use of the service, as detailed in section 4 below. Our arrangements with third-party service providers and online vendors should ensure that Your privacy is protected.

**4\. INFORMATION USE** (back to top)

4.1 The personal information collected from You will be used:

  * to deliver the service;
  * to provide customer support;
  * to undertake necessary security and identity verification checks;
  * to meet certain business requirements; and
  * for any other purpose related to the operation of the service.

4.2 Affiliates, subsidiaries, agents and suppliers may also share Your personal information in order to provide the service. These groups may also supply promotional offers and information regarding the company, our group of companies and the service.

4.3 We or our affiliates, subsidiaries, agents and suppliers may occasionally request information from You using surveys or contests. Participation is completely voluntary and You therefore have the choice of whether or not to disclose such information. Information requested may include:

  * contact information, such as name, correspondence address and telephone number; and
  * demographic information such as postal code or age

 4.4 If You subsequently win a survey or contest, and accept a prize or winnings, You are consenting to the use of Your name, screen-name (where applicable), image, photographs, and general locations for advertising, promotional and news purposes without additional compensation, except where prohibited by law.   
4.5 Personal information, such as e-mail address and telephone number, may also be used where You have agreed to receive promotional material. This will provide You with details of any similar products, services and promotions supplied by ourselves or our affiliates, including other online gaming products such as casino and bingo.  
We will not sell, lease or share Your personal information except as detailed in this Privacy Policy. At account closure, Your data will be kept for a certain period for legal and accounting purposes and will then be removed from our system.

4.6 In order to play Real Money games You will need a facility to send and receive money. Third Party electronic payment processors and/or financial institutions may be used to process such financial transactions ("ESPs"). By accepting this Privacy Policy You agree to the sharing of necessary personal information, with the ESPs, to enable the processing of transactions. Where necessary, this may include the transfer of information outside of Your country, which may not have been classified as having acceptable privacy laws.  
We use all reasonable endeavours to ensure that our arrangements with ESPs protect Your privacy.  
4.7 You agree that we are permitted to share personal information and all other information You may have provided by using the service, to potential and subsequent business and merger partners, if we undertake the following:

  * file for bankruptcy;
  * acquisition by a third party;
  * merge with a third party;
  * sell all or part of our assets; or
  * transfer substantially all of our relevant assets to a third party.

**5\. ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION** (back to top)

5.1 By sending an e-mail to help@galacasino.com, or calling us on 0800 328 4272 (Monday-Sunday between 7am and 11pm), or by writing to GalaCasino.com Customer Services, Globe House, Victoria Way, Woking GU21 6DD, You can organise the following: (link to Contact Us section on Help Page) ****

  * stop promotional communications by either opting out on the websites, where applicable, or in an e-mail received from us;
  * confirm the accuracy of the personal information we have collected on You;
  * update or delete Your personal information;
  * lodge a complaint regarding the use of Your personal information; or
  * change any information provided to us or mark any information to prohibit future use, provided evidence is provided to support such changes.

**6\. C** **OOKIES** (back to top)

6.1 Cookies are small text files that record Your preferences when You visit certain online pages, and are stored on Your compu **t** er or equipment. We use cookies to:

  * track the use of the service;
  * monitor traffic to the service; and
  * improve the service by making it easier and more relevant for You.

6.2 Online browsers can usually be set to either accept or decline cookies. However if cookies are declined You may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the service.

**7\. C** **ONSENT TO SECURITY REVIEW** (back to top)

7.1 We may conduct a security review at any time to confirm Your identity, age and the registration data provided by You. This information will be used to verify use of Your account and financial transactions for potential breach of our terms and of applicable law.  
7.2 By accepting this Privacy Policy, You authorise us, our staff, affiliates, subsidiaries, agents and suppliers to both use Your personal information and to disclose Your personal information to third parties with the objective of validating the supplied information. This includes where necessary the transfer of information outside of Your country, including to countries whose privacy laws may not be regarded as acceptable.  
7.3 Security reviews may include, but are not limited to, ordering a credit report and/or confirming supplied information against third party databases. In addition, information or documentation may be requested to assist with these security reviews.

**8\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION** (back to top)

8.1 Information security is important to us and we understand the techniques required to secure this information. Security measures are in place to protect Your information from access by unauthorised persons and to prevent unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage.  
8.2 Data on our secure pages is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology. Personal information received directly from You will be stored in a password-protected database located within our secure network behind active state of the art firewall software.  
8.3 Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet cannot be completely secure at all times. Although we will make every reasonable effort to protect Your personal information, it cannot guarantee the security of any information disclosed online. In opening an account with us, You accept the potential security risks of internet use and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless it has been proved that we have been negligent. For Your own privacy protection we encourage You not to include sensitive information, for example credit/debit cards, in any e-mails sent to us.  
8.4 **** The Service operates "AS-IS" and "AS-AVAILABLE," without liability of any kind **.** Whilst we have implemented appropriate technical and organisational measures to ensure the safety of Your personal information, due to the continually evolving state of technology and business, coupled with its complexity, we are not able to guarantee error-free performance in relation to the privacy of Your personal information. ****

**8.5** Protection of any information or images provided to a third-party online site that links to or from the service, cannot be guaranteed. This includes information collected by any third party managing our affiliate program or any other program, as these third-party online sites are owned and operated independently of us. ****

8.6 **** Information gathered by these third parties will fall under their privacy policy rather than ours. If You have any queries regarding a third party's privacy policy, You can obtain this information directly from them. ****

8.7 We are not responsible or liable for:

  * the actions or policies of these third parties; or ****
  * the content or privacy practices of these online sites.

**9\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS** (back to top)

9.1 Personal information collected on the service may be stored and processed in any country in which we or our affiliates, suppliers, subsidiaries or agents have facilities. By using the service, You agree to the transfer of Your personal information outside of Your country, including to countries which may not have been reviewed as having acceptable privacy laws. Nevertheless, all reasonable processes are in place to ensure that our affiliates, agents, subsidiaries and suppliers comply with our privacy standards, irrespective of location.

**10\. CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY** (back to top)

10.1 You agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy if You complete the following:

  * by clicking the box next to "I accept the Terms & Conditions (incorporating the Privacy Policy)" during the registration process;
  * by continued use of the service following the posting of this Privacy Policy

10.2 This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our terms and any additional applicable terms posted on our websites. Changes may be made to this Privacy Policy from time to time. In the event that there are any changes, an updated version of our Privacy Policy will be published on our websites.  
Last amended on 24th April 2012, this, our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy, supersedes all previous versions.
